telebrands.net 2014-04-24

# Telebrands ™ | Official Site | The Original “As Seen On TV” Company

Information About You:  
We collect several types of information on our Site. We collect "Personal Information", which generally speaking is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name and address. We also collect "Non-personal Information", which is information about you that does not itself identify you individually. Examples of Non-personal Information include age range and gender. We also collect "Aggregate Information", which is information about use of our site, such as pages visited on our Site. The information we collect depends on what services you use on our Site.

Customer Service Correspondence:  
We may collect information that identifies you personally when you submit comments, questions or suggestions to our Customer Service department.

Use of Your Personal and Non-Personal Information:  
Except as disclosed in this policy, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies our guests personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly without our guests' consent. We may use, sell, disclose, or otherwise dispose of Personal Information we collect in the following circumstances:

Internal Analysis and Promotions:   
We may use information about you for our own internal statistical, design, operational purposes such as to estimate our audience size; measure aggregate traffic patterns; and understand demographic, customer interest, purchasing and other trends among our guests and customers. We may also use your Personal Information for the marketing and/or promotion of our products or services. We may outsource all of these tasks to third parties on a confidential basis. If you have received an email from any members of the Telebrands Corporation, and you wish to no longer receive emails, please click the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email. You will receive a confirmation email in which you will find a link that you must click on in order to complete the unsubscribe process.

Co-Branded Service Offerings:   
We may share this information with certain businesses with whom Telebrands has formed a strategic alliance. You may be able to identify these businesses because Telebrands has authorized them to display co-branded Web pages or links to Telebrands. These strategic partners are requested to clearly state their own privacy policies on their own web sites or promotional materials. If you do not want to have your personal information shared with these businesses you may click here.

Transaction Processing:   
We may use your Personal Information to create a convenient and easy-to-use shopping process that includes an online "shopping cart" that allows you to track selected products and proceed through purchase. Also we may share transactional information with entities as is necessary to process credit card payments or other purchasing or delivery systems.

Third-Party Offers:   
We may arrange to have marketing and promotional information of other companies sent to you that we think might be of interest to you.

Legal Requirement:   
We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform with the law, respond to claims or comply with legal process served on our company or the Site; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Site, our employees, guests or the public.

Company Sale:   
Information collected through our Site is considered a trade secret of Telebrands. As the owner of such information, we may disclose or sell such information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale to a third party of our company or a portion of our assets.

Links to Other Sites:   
Please be aware that we provide links to third-party Web sites as a service to our guests, and that we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those pages. Please note that these Web sites' privacy policies may differ from those of Telebrands. We encourage your to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.

Children:   
Our Site is a general audience site that is not designed nor intended to collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any Personal Information on this Site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.
